Guide to the Peninsula-Times Tribune Photographs of Stanford University PC0065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Peninsula-Times Tribune photographs of Stanford University
1959-1992
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Peninsula Times Tribune.
PC0065
4 Linear Feet
These photographs pertaining to Stanford University were selected from the morgue of the Peninsula Times-Tribune after its closing. They consist of photographs by the newspaper staff as well as photographs obtained from the Stanford News Service and other sources.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Peninsula-Times Tribune was organized in April 1979 from a merger of the Palo Alto Times and the Redwood City Tribune, both owned by the parent company Peninsula Newspapers Incorported. The paper ceased publishing in 1993.
Description of the Collection
These photographs pertaining to Stanford University were selected from the morgue of the Peninsula Times-Tribune after its closing. They consist of photographs by the newspaper staff as well as photographs obtained from the Stanford News Service and other sources. The bulk of the images are from the early 1970s through 1992; there are also a few copy prints of historical photographs. Subjects include administrators, employees, faculty, buildings, campus life, commencement, construction, Hoover Institution, the Medical Center, sports, politicians and events on campus, Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, the Stanford Shopping Center, student life, and demonstrations.
Index
Abernethy, David 3 9
Abrams, Herbert L. 3 9
Abrica, Ruben 3 3
Abzug, Bella 2 12
Adler, Alan 3 9
Akiyama, Diana 3 9
Alejo, Francisco 3 1
Ambrogi, Thomas 3 9
Anderson, Martin 2 12
Anderson, Martin 3 9
Angell, Jim 3 9
Aragon, Al 3 9
Arbuckle, Ernest 3 9
Archuleta, Keith 1 1
Arias, Oscar 3 8
Arrow, Kenneth 3 9
Atwood, Bill 7 14
Babbitt, Bruce 2 12
Babcock, Barbara 3 10
Bacon, Harold and Rosamond 3 10
Bagshaw, Malcom 7 14
Bailey, Thomas A. 3 10
Banks, Peter 3 10
Baratz, Michael 1 1
Barhoum, Khalil 3 10
Bark, William C. 3 10
Barnes, Arthur 1 1
Barnes, Arthur 3 10
Barnette, Rodney 1 1
Barwise, Jon 4 4
Bean, Randy 1 4
Beasley, Malcolm 7 7
Becker, Gary 5 6
Beinen, Joel 3 10
Bell, Derrick 3 10
Bennett, William 2 12
Berg, Paul 3 10
Berggren, Bo 2 16
Berghouse-Hicks, Janoda 4 1
Biafra, Jello 2 12
Biddle, Paul 1 17
Bienenstock, Arthur 3 10
Bienenstock, Arthur 7 7
Bin, Yu 3 10
Bing, Peter S. 1 1
Bing, Peter S. 5 6
Blacker, Coit 1 4
Blacker, Coit 3 10
Bland, Byron 3 6
Blank, Norman 3 10
Bliven, Bruce and Rosie 2 4
Bloch, Felix 3 10
Bloem, Kenneth 1 1
Bloem, Kenneth 3 6
Blume, Karl G. 3 10
Bocek, Barbara 2 1
Boesak, Allan 2 12
Boskin, Michael 3 10
Boudart, Michel 3 10
Bowen, Jose 2 12
Bowman, Richard 2 12
Boyle, Eugene 1 1
Bracewell, John 3 10
Brademas, John 1 1
Brafort, David 3 10
Brand, Carl 3 10
Brandin, Alf 1 1
Breakwell, John 3 10
Breitrose, Henry 3 10
Brest, Paul 1 1
Brickman, Gary 2 12
Brinner, William 2 12
Britt, Deborah 1 1
Brokaw, Tom 2 12
Brower, David 3 10
Brown, Jerry 7 3
Brown, John Russell 3 10
Brown, Robert McAfee 3 10
Brown, Stephanie 1 1
Buma, Maurine 1 1
Burciaga, Antonio 3 10
Burress, Richard 5 6
Buss, Claude 3 10
Calos, Michele 7 7
Camarillo, Albert 3 11
Campbell, Glenn 5 4
Campbell, Tom 1 19
Campell, Ross 1 1
Canger, Charlene 1 1
Cannon, Robert 3 11
Cannon, Robert 7 7
Carlsmith, Merrill 3 11
Carlson, Gretchen 8 9
Carnoy, Martin 2 13
Carson, Clayborne 7 6
Cartun, Ari 3 11
Casper, Gerhard 2 6
Casper, Regina 2 6
Cates, Williard 2 13
Cavalli, Gary 8 12
Chen, Terry 3 11
Chodorow, Nancy 2 13
Chowning, John 3 11
Christiansen, Dorothy 1 1
Christopher, Warren 1 1
Clark, Dwight 1 1
Clark, Ed 2 13
Clark, Ramsey 2 13
Clements, Charles 3 11
Cleveland, Barbara 1 1
Cleveland, William 1 1
Closson, Michael 2 13
Cogan, John 5 6
Cohen, Bernard 3 11
Cohen, Harvey 1 1
Cohen, Stanley N. 3 11
Cohn, Ray 2 13
Cohn, Robert 3 11
Coladarci, Arthur 3 11
Coleman, Richard 7 7
Collman, James 3 11
Collopy, Michelle 1 1
Conlan, Francis 3 11
Conley, Frances 3 11, 15
Cook, Perry 7 7
Cox, Allen 3 11
Cuomo, Mario 4 13
Curry, Jack 2 13
D'Andrea, Vince 3 12
D'Souza, Dinesh 2 14
Dallin, Alexander 3 12
Dallmar, Howie 3 12
Dallmar, Howie Jr. 2 14
Daneke, Greg 3 12
Danelski, David 3 12
Dangl, Jeff 3 12
Daniloff, Nicholas 2 14
David, Paul 3 12
Davis, Angela 2 14
Davis, Joseph 3 12
Davis, Kingsley 3 12
Davis, Margo 1 2
Davis, Robert 3 12
Dawidowitz, Lucy 3 12
de Coteau, Denis 2 14
de la Rosa, Evelyn 2 14
de Necochea, Fernando 3 12
DeBra, Daniel 3 12
Decleve, Alain 1 2
Degler, Carl 2 14
Delbecq, Andre L. 1 2
DeLeeuw, Sita 3 12
Delisco, Peter 3 12
Dement, William 7 7
Dement, William 3 12
DePalma, Brian 2 14
Di Sario, Paul 3 12
Diaconis, Persi 3 12
Ditz, Nancy 7 11
Dixon, Dorothy 1 2
Dong, Eugene 3 12
Doobie Brothers 2 14
Dornbush, Sanford 3 12
Dorosin, David 1 2
Doty, Andy 1 2
Drake, St. Clair 2 14
Drell, Sidney 2 14
Drell, Sidney 7 14
Dreyfus, John 3 19
Duckworth, Penelope 3 12
Duignan, Peter 5 6
Dunlop, John B. 5 6
Dura, George 3 12
Durenberger, Dave 7 3
Dutton, Robert 3 12
Edwards, Walter G. 2 15
Efron, Bradley 3 13
Eisenstadt, S. N. 5 6
Elkus, Dick 3 6
Ellickson, Robert 3 13
Ellsberg, Daniel 2 15
Elsen, Albert 3 13
Elway, Jack 1 2
Elway, Jack 1 4
Elway, Jack 3 13
Ely, John Hart 1 2
Engleman, Edgar G. 3 13
Englund, Vicki 1 2
Everitt, Francis 3 13
Fackenheim, Emil 3 14
Fainberg, Anthony 3 14
Fairbank, William 3 13, 14
Falcon, Walter 3 14
Fariello, Lois 1 2
Farley, Phillip 3 14
Farquar, John W. 3 14
Feigenbaum, Edward 3 14
Feinstein, Dianne 4 11
Feldman, Gary 3 14
Felstiner, John 3 14
Felstiner, Mary 3 14
Ferejohn, John 5 6
Fetter, Jean 1 2
Fields, Gitta 3 14
Fields, Kenneth W. 3 14
Fisher, Harold H. 3 14
Fitzgerald, George 1 2
Flory, Paul 3 14
Floyd, Mary 3 14
Food-Service employees 1 8
Ford, Gerald 3 8
Ford, John B. 1 2
Ford, Thomas W. 2 15
Fortmann, Stephen 1 2
Foster, John 2 16
Foung, Steven 3 14
Frausto, Thomas Ybarra 3 14
Frederik, Crown Prince 2 15
Free, Helen 4 1
Freelen, Robert 1 2
Freeman, Roger 3 14
French, Gordon 3 14
Friedan, Betty 2 15
Friedland, Peter 2 15
Friedman, Milton 5 6
Friendly, Fred 2 15
Fries, James 3 14
Fu, Weitan 4 2
Fuchs, Henry 3 14
Fuchs, Victor R. 3 14
Fuenzalida, Edmundo 1 2
Fullerton, Gail 1 2
Gaither, James 1 3
Gardner, Jim 3 15
Gardner, John W. 2 15
Gardner, John W. 3 15
Gardner, Larry 1 3
Garfield, Emily 1 3
Garriott, Owen 2 16
Garrow, David 2 16
Gedde, Yemane 3 15
Geiger, Andy 1 3
Geiger, Andy 3 15
Gelber, Steven 3 15
Gelles, Edith 3 15
George, Alexander 3 15
George, Juliette 3 15
Gere, James 3 6
Gere, James 3 15
Gerstel, Martin 3 15
Gibbons, James 1 3
Gielitz, Carl ("Captain Midnight") 1 3
Ginzton, Edward 2 17
Giraud, Raymond 3 15
Giscard d'Estaing, Valery 3 8
Glantz, Stanton 2 16
Glaser, Robert 1 5
Gobran, Brian 3 16
Goldberg, Whoopi 2 7
Gonda, Thomas A. 3 15
Gonda, Thomas A. 4 5
Goodall, Jane 2 16
Goodkind, Mike 1 3
Goodman, Corey 3 15
Gorbachev, Mikhail 4 12
Gore, Albert Jr. 2 16
Gore, Albert Jr. 7 3
Gould, Dick 3 15
Gould, William B. 3 15
Gray, Kathy 7 7
Green, Dennis 5 3
Greenberg, Harry 3 15
Greenberg, Joseph 3 15
Greenberg, Peter 3 15
Greenfield, Anne 3 15
Greenfield, Christopher 3 15
Greenfield, Jonathon 3 15
Grissom, Grady 8 9
Groethe, Peter 3 15
Gross, Richard 3 15
Grumet, F. Carl 3 15
Gunther, Gerald 3 15
Gur, Turgut M. 3 15
Gustaf, Carl XVI [King] 2 16
Gustafson, Michael L. 3 15
Habib, Philip 5 6
Hagstrom, Stig 3 16
Hall, Robert 5 6
Halton, Donald 3 16
Hamerton-Kelly, Robert G. 1 3
Hamerton-Kelly, Robert G. 2 16
Hamill, Robin 1 3
Hamilton, Cynthia 2 13
Hamilton, H.J. Belton 2 16
Hammer, Armand 3 4
Hampson, V. Stanford 1 3
Hamrdla, Bob 2 16
Hanawalt, Philip C. 3 16
Hanna, Paul 1 8
Hanna, Paul 5 6
Hansen, Ralph 1 3
Hanson, Kirk 3 16
Harbaugh, Jack 3 16
Hargadon, Fred 1 3
Harlan, Neil 3 15
Harrell, Thomas 3 16
Harrington, John 1 3
Harris, Prof. David 3 16
Harris, David [alumni, politician] 4 14
Harrison, Donald C. 3 16
Harrison, Robert 2 16
Hastorf, Albert 1 3
Hastorf, Albert 3 16
Hay, Joel 5 6
Hayakawa, S. I. 5 6
Hayden, Tom 2 16
Hayden, Tom 8 6
Hayes, Dennis 2 16
Hedman, David 1 3
Heinrichs, W. LeRoy 3 16
Heller, Craig 3 16
Heller, Thomas 3 16
Helliwell, Robert 3 19
Hellman, Martin 3 16
Hennessy, John 3 16
Henriksen, Thomas 3 16
Hermanns, William 3 16
Hess, Robert 3 16
Hess quadruplets 6 9
Hester, Ralph 3 16
Hilton, Ronald 3 16
Hoadley, Walter 3 16
Hodel, Donald 1 3
Hook, Sidney 5 6
Hoover, Edgar 5 6
Horn, Alvah 3 16
Horton, Larry 3 16
Huerta, Mario 2 16
Huff, Robert 1 3
Huggins, Robert 3 16
Humphrey, Hubert 7 3
Islas, Arturo 3 17
Jackson, Jesse 7 3
Jackson, Kenneth 4 6
Jackson, Shauna 1 4
Jacob, Paul 2 17
Jaedicke, Robert 1 4
Jaedicke, Robert K. 3 18
James, Olive 1 4
Jameson, Michael 3 18
Jedd, Joseph 1 4
Jemison, Mae 2 17
Jennison, M. Harry 3 18
Johnson, Clifford 1 4
Johnson, Dick 1 4
Johnson, Steve 1 4
Johnston, Bruce 2 17
Johnstone, Joann 1 4
Jones, Patricia 3 18
Jordan, David Starr 5 10
Jordan, June 2 16
Jordan, Payton 1 4
Jurian, Frank 1 4
Kamenev, Valentin 2 17
Kaplan, David 1 4
Kaplan, Dorothy 3 19
Kaplan, Henry 3 19
Kaplan, John 3 19
Kaplan, Leah 1 4
Katchadourian, Herant 3 19
Katsufrakis, John 3 19
Kaye, Danny 2 17
Keller, Ralph W. 1 4
Kelly, Kate 2 17
Kelly, Leontine T.C. 2 17
Kennedy, Anthony 2 17
Kennedy, Donald 1 3
Kennedy, Donald 1 4
Kennedy, Donald 2 6
Kennedy, Donald 2 15, 16
Kennedy, Donald 5 11
Kennedy, Edward 7 3
Kennedy, Jeanne 1 4
Kennedy, Jeanne 5 11
Keohane, Nan 3 19
Keohane, Robert 3 19
Kiam, Victor 2 17
Kim, Ki Sung 2 16
Kimball, William 1 4
King, Bill 8 9
King, Coretta Scott 2 17
King, Victoria 6 6
King, Sheldon 6 6
Kirkpatrick, Paul 3 19
Kirst, Michael 3 19
Kmetovic, Helen 1 4
Knuth, Donald 3 19
Kohn, Alexander 3 19
Koppel, Ted 2 7
Korn, David 1 4
Kraus, Kathy 1 4
Kuhn, Wolfgang 3 19
Kurz, Mordecai 1 4
L'Heureux, John 3 20
Lamb, Emmett J. 3 20
Lapid, Gary 3 20
Laskowicz 1 11
Lawrence, Kathy 1 4
Leavitt, Harold 3 20
Leighton, Michelle 1 8
Lerman, Louis 3 20
Levertov, Denise 2 17
Levin, Henry 1 4
Levin, Joseph 2 17
Levy, Ronald 3 20
Lewenstein, Marion 3 20
Lewis, Amy Tucker 4 4
Lewis, John 1 4
Lewis, John 3 20
Lewis, Lovie 1 4
Li, Victor 3 20
Lightfoot, Sara Lawrence 3 20
Lillie, John 1 4
Linvill, John 3 20
Lipa, John 7 7
Lipset, Seymour Martin 5 7
Lisac, Andrew 1 4
Little, Judith 1 4
Little, William [physics] 7 7
Little, William A. 3 20
Liu, James 3 20
Long, Sharon 3 20
Lopez, Israel 1 3
Lopez, Leonard 6 5
Love, John N. 1 4
Lucas, C. Payne 2 17
Luce, Don 2 17
Lunde, Donald 3 20
Lyman, Jing 2 17
Lyman, Richard 1 4
Lyon, Charles 3 20
M'Bow, Amador Mahtar 3 1
Machein, Kurt 4 1
Manley, John 4 1
Mansout, Tag E. 4 1
Mantooth, Betty 1 5
Mardique, M. 4 1
Mark, James B. D. 4 1
Markman, Ellen 4 1
Marquart, Ann 1 5
Marshall, Hubert 4 1
Marshall, Rachelle 4 1
Marson, Charles 4 1
Martinez, Alejandro 4 1
Massey, William 1 3
Massy, William 1 5
Mathews, Max 4 1
Mathias, Bob 7 11
Matin, Abdul 4 1
Maynard, Robert C. 3 1
Mazour, Anatole 4 1
McAndrews, Rosemary 1 5
McBride, Thomas 3 1
McCarthy, John 4 1
McDonald, J. 1 5
McDougall, Ross 4 1
McFerrin, Bobby 2 7
McGlashan, Doug and Ricki 3 16
McGovern, George 7 3
McKean, Susan 1 5
McKernan, Kathy 1 5
McMullen, John 1 5
McPherson, Rene 4 1
Medicine, Anne 4 1
Meese, Edwin 5 7
Meier, Gretl 1 5
Mengozzi, Paolo 3 1
Meyer, Gerald 4 1
Meyers, Charles J. 4 1
Meyer, Russ 4 1
Michelson, Peter 7 7
Middlebrook, Diane 4 1
Mielke, Frederick W. 1 5
Miller, Arjay 4 1
Miller, Frank 4 1
Miller, Rupert 4 1
Miller, William F. 4 1
Milton, Chris 8 9
Milton, Catherine 3 1
Mitchell, Ted 1 5
Moe, Terry 4 1
Moldestad, John 1 5
Moller, Gerald 1 5
Mooney, Harold 4 1
Mooney, Sean 4 1
Moore, Marvin 1 5
Moore, Mary 1 5
Moore, Thomas G. 5 7
Moos, Rudolf H. 4 1
Morgan, Barbara 3 1
Morris, Kate 8 9
Morton, Dean 1 5
Mosher, Carol 4 1
Mosher, Harry 4 1
Mosher, Stephen 8 9
Muggeridge, Malcolm 3 1
Muller, Niki 4 1
Munger, Nancy 1 5
Munter, Mary 1 5
Munter, Mary 3 1
Munzer, Rudolph 1 5
Murad, Ferid 4 1
Murphy, Dennis 4 1
Murray, Douglas P. 4 1
Myers, Herbert 1 5
Myers, Ramon 4 1
Nader, Ralph 3 2
Nanney, Herbert 1 5
Nathan, Joel 1 5
Nelson, Warren 4 2
Nerrie, Robert 1 5
Newell, Thomas M. 4 2
Newman, Frank 1 5
Newman-Gordon, Pauline 4 2
Nilan, Roxanne 1 5
Nixon, Richard 3 2
Northway, William H. 4 2
Noyes, James 5 7
Nur, Amos 4 2
O'Brien, Bill 3 16
O'Connor, Sandra Day 3 3
O'Connor, Sandra Day 4 13
Oakford, Robert 4 3
Oakland Symphony Pops Orchestra 3 3
Obery, Ron 1 6
Obledo, Mario 3 3
Ogilvie, June 1 6
Okimoto, Daniel 1 6
Olcott, Phoebe 3 15
Olefsky, Jerrold 4 3
Oliveira, Nathan 4 3
Olson, Charles 1 6
Organ, Henry 1 6
Organ, Henry 3 3
Orloff, Jann 1 6
Osheroff, Douglas 4 3
Ott, Wayne 4 3
Owete, Owete S. 3 16
Oyer, Philip E. 4 3
Packer, Nancy 4 4
Paffenbarger Jr., Ralph S. 4 4
Palm, Charles 5 7
Panofsky, Adele 4 4
Panofsky, Wolfgang 7 14
Papp, Richard 4 4
Parker, Robert 1 3
Parker, Sharon 1 6
Parks, Rosa 3 4
Paul, Diana 4 4
Pauling, Linus 2 14
Pauling, Linus 2 17
Pauling, Linus 3 4
Paulsen, Sue 1 6
Payne, Rose 4 4
Payton, Sallyanne 1 6
Peace Child Group Choir 3 4
Pearson, John 4 4
Pearson, Lionel 4 4
Peck, Templeton 1 14
Pecorino, John 3 4
Pendleton, Clarence 4 4
Peng, Li 7 3
Perez, Eddie 1 10
Perkins, Edward 3 4
Perloff, Marjorie 4 4
Perry, Arlis 1 6
Perry, John 4 4
Peters, Tom 4 8
Phillips, John 4 4
Pitzer, Kenneth 1 6
Pitzer, Kenneth 4 4
Polan, Mary Lake 4 4
Poland, Joseph 4 4
Polhemus, Patrica 1 6
Polland, Harry 4 4
Polya, George 4 4
Pont, Allan 4 4
Popp, Richard L. 4 4
Portner, Peer M. 4 4
Preservation Hall Jazz Band 3 4
Press, Harry 1 6
Prigogine, Ilya 3 4
Prince, David 4 4
Princess Marie 3 4
Princess Paola 3 4
Pringle, Stuart 3 4
Pritchard, Michael 3 4
Purpura, Dominick 1 6
Quate, Calvin 2 16
Quist, Chad 3 16
Rabushka, Alvin 5 7
Rader, Rosemary 4 5
Raffel, Sidney 4 5
Rafshoon, Gerald 3 5
Raisian, John 5 7
Raitt, James W. 4 5
Ralston, Ted 4 5
Ramsey, Wiliam 3 5
Rathbun, Harry J. 4 5
Ratliff, William 5 7
Raubitschek, Antony 4 5
Raubitschek, Isabelle 4 5
Raushenbakh, Boris 3 16
Raymond, Steven 4 5
Reaven, Gerald 4 5
Rebholz, Ronald 4 1
Rebholz, Ronald 4 5
Reges, Stuart 4 5
Reid, Brian K. 4 5
Reimers, Neil 1 7
Reitz, Bruce 4 5
Reyden, Halsey 4 5
Reyes, Geronimo 1 7
Reyna, George 1 7
Reynolds, Clark 3 1
Ricardo-Campell, Rita 3 4
Ricardo-Campell, Rita 4 5
Rice, Condoleezza 1 4
Rice, Condoleezza 2 13
Rice, John 1 4
Richardson, Jack 4 8
Richter, Burton 7 14
Ride, Sally 1 14
Riggs, Henry 1 7
Roberts, Don 4 5
Robertson, Greg 4 5
Robin, Eugene 4 5
Robinson, Randall 3 5
Robinson, William 4 5
Rodinov, Leonid 3 6
Rohrabacher, Dana 3 5
Rooney, Andy 3 5
Rosaldo, Michelle 4 5
Rosenberg, Rina 1 7
Rosenberg, Saul A. 4 5
Rosenfeld, Ron G. 4 5
Rosenzweig, Robert 1 7
Rosse, James 1 7
Rosse, Stuart 1 4
Rothenberg, Annye 6 4
Roughgarden, Jonathan 4 5
Rowen, Henry S. 4 5
Rowen, Henry S. 5 7
Ruark, John E. 3 15
Ruark, John E. 4 5
Rubbia, Carlo 3 5
Ruetz, Joseph H. 1 7
Rumberger, Russell 1 4
Rumberger, Russell 4 5
Ryan, Lawrence V. 4 5
Ryan, Michael 1 7
Sagan, Carl 3 6
Salinger, Pierre 3 6
Sapolsky, Robert 4 6
Sapolsky, Robert 7 7
Sarnquist, Frank 4 6
Sarris, Greg 4 6
Schawlow, Arthur L. 4 6
Schawlow, Aurelia 4 6
Schawlow, Helen 4 6
Schimke, Robert 4 6
Schimmel, Nancy 8 12
Schindler, Craig 4 6
Schmidt, Harold 4 6
Schmidt, Helmut 3 8
Schoolnik, Gary 4 6
Schreck, Evelyn 1 8
Schrier, Stanley L. 3 6
Schulman, Irving 1 8
Schulman, Irving 4 6
Schwartz, John [Univ. lawyer] 1 8
Schwartz, John J. [Med. School] 1 8
Seale, Bobby 3 6
Sears, Robert 4 6
Seaver, John 4 6
Seaver, Paul 4 6
Sebera, Wayne 2 15
Seligman, Thomas 1 8
Selmon, Greg 4 6
Seltzer, Leon 1 8
Semprini, Lou 1 8
Seth, Vikram 1 14
Shah, Haresh 3 6
Shah, Haresh 3 15
Shapiro, Lucy 4 6
Sharpe, William F. 4 6
Shasky, Florian 1 8
Shavone, Rick 1 8
Shaw, Ed 1 8
Shaw, Ed 4 6
Shaw, John 4 6
Sheehan, James 1 4
Shelton, Judy 5 7
Shing-Tung Yau 1 8
Shockley, William 4 6
Shooter, Eric M. 4 6
Shortliffe, Edward 4 6
Shoven, John B. 4 6
Shultz, George 5 5
Shultz, George 7 8
Shumway, Norman 4 5
Sidorov, Viktor 3 6
Sikic, Branimir 4 6
Simpson, Carol 4 6
Simpson, Peter 4 6
Skelton, Red 3 6
Sklar, Jeffrey 4 6
Sleazak, Linda 1 8
Sloan, Elizabeth 1 8
Slusser, Susan 8 9
Smith, Edward 1 8
Smith, Joel 1 8
Smith, Marshall 1 8
Smith, Peter 3 1
Smith, Stephen 4 6
Snyder, Rixford K. 4 6
Snyder, Steve 3 6
Soforenko, Ruth 1 8
Sokol, Anthony 4 6
Sokolow, Sonja 1 8
Solomon, Ezra 4 6
Sorensen, Ted 3 6
Soroka, Barry 7 7
Sowell, Thomas 4 6
Spence, A. Michael 1 8
Spiegel, David 4 6
Spindler, George D. 4 6
Spitz, Lewis 4 6
Spitzer, Robert 4 6
Spivack, Alfred P. 6 5
Spock, Benjamin 3 6
Staar, Richard F. 5 7
Starnes, Vaughn 4 6
Stegner, Wallace 8 2
Steinem, Gloria 3 6
Sterling, Bill 3 6
Sterling, J.E. Wallace 8 3
Stewart, Alan 4 6
Stewart, Eleanor 1 8
Still, Clair 1 8
Stinson, Edward B. 4 6
Stockdale, James 3 6
Stone, William E. 1 14
Strachota, Katjryn 4 6
Strathairn, Pamela L. 1 8
Streleski, Theodore 6 12
Strober, Myra 4 6
Stryer, Andrea 6 11
Sturua, George 3 6
Sullivan, Louis L. 3 6
Sunsei, Mary V. 1 8
Suppes, Patrick 4 6
Sutton, Marge 1 8
Svoda, Roger 4 6
Sweeney, James 4 6
Swidler, Ann 4 6
Tajnai, Carolyn 2 15
Talley, Jerry 4 7
Tansey, Pam 3 7
Tansey, Pat 3 7
Tarter, Helen 1 9
Tatum, Frank 1 9
Taube, Henry 4 7
Taube, Mary 4 7
Taylor, Richard 7 14
Tearley, Lee H. 4 9
Teece, David J. 4 7
Teller, Edward 5 7
Terman, Fred E. 4 7
Terman, Fred E. 8 3
Thomas, Debi 3 7
Thomas, Ewart 1 9
Thomas, Lewis 1 9
Thomas, Warren 3 7
Thompson, David 4 7
Thompson, Hunter. 3 7
Thoresen, Carl 4 7
Tolomei, Gene 1 9
Trudeau, Gary 4 13
Tuma, Nancy Brandon 4 7
Turner, Laura 6 6
Tyler, Leonard 4 7
Van Andel, Tjeerd 4 8
Van Etten, Peter 1 10
Van Seters, Jacques 3 15
Van Campen, Joseph 4 8
Voll, Peter 1 10
Wachtell, Jeff 1 10
Walker, Arthur 4 8
Walker, Duane 1 10
Walsh, Bill 4 8
Walter, John 3 16
Walters, Paul 4 8
Ward, Robert 4 8
Wasow, Thomas A. 1 10
Wasow, Thomas A. 4 8
Waxman, Stephen 4 8
Webb, Elnora 1 10
Webb, Eugene 1 4
Webb, Eugene 1 10
Webb, Eugene 4 8
Webster, William 4 8
Weiner, Stephen 4 8
Werry, Ann 3 16
Wessels, Norman 4 8
Wesson, Robert 4 8
Westheimer, Ruth 3 8
Whitaker, Gary 3 8
White, Byron 3 8
White, Robert 4 8
Whitehouse, Harry T. 4 8
Wicker, Tom 3 8
Wiggans, Bruce 1 10
Wiggin, Paul 1 10
Wilcox, Bruce 4 8
Wilcox, John 4 8
Williams, Lloyd 8 9
Williams, Phil 1 8
Wills, Babette 1 10
Wilson, Andrea 4 8
Wilson, Pete 2 7
Winkler, John 4 8
Winograd, Leonard 4 8
Wojcicki, Stanley G. 4 8
Wolfe, Bertran 4 8
Ybarra-Frausto, Thomas 4 9
Yew, Lee Kuan 3 8
Young, Ernie 4 9
Young, James 2 16
Zaffaroni, Alejandro 3 15
Zalewski, Wodciech 1 11
Zapf, Hermann 3 19
Zatz, Leslie M. 4 10
Zdarko, Richard 7 14
Zeigler, Lee 4 10
Zelditch, Bernce 4 10
Zimbardo, Philip 4 10
Zschau, Ed 3 8
Photoprints.; Peninsula Times Tribune.; Stanford University. Department of Athletics; Peninsula Times Tribune.; Stanford University. Medical Center; Stanford Shopping Center.; Stanford Linear Accelerator Center; Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace
- Photographs, 1959-1992
  - Administrators-Employees [A-C] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrators-Employees [D-F] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrators-Employees [G-I] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrators-Employees [J-L] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrators-Employees [M-N] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administrators-Employees [O-Q] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrators-Employees [R] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrators-Employees [S] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administrators-Employees [T] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrators-Employees [V-W] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administrators-Employees [X-Z] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrators-Employees [Misc.] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aerials (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumni and Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Art [1] (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Art [2] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Biddle, Paul (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Buildings (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Campbell, Tom (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Campus [1] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Campus [2] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Campus [3] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Campus [4] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Campus Life [1] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Campus Life [2] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Casper, Gerhard (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Centennial 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Conferences (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Construction (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Donors (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ethnic Culture (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Events [A-B] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Events [C] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Events [D] (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Events [E-F] (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Events [G-I] (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Events [J-L] (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Events [M] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Events [N] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Events [O] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Events [P] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Events [R] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Events [S] (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Events [T] (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Events [W-Z] (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty [A] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Faculty [B] (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Faculty [C] (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faculty [D] (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty [E] (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Faculty [F] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Faculty [G] (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Faculty [H] (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Faculty [I] (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Faculty [J] (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Faculty [K] (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Faculty [L] (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Faculty [M] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Faculty [N] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty [O] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty [P] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty [R] (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Faculty [S] (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Faculty [T] (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Faculty [V-W] (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Faculty [Y] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faculty [Z] (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Feinstein, Dianne (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Graduations (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Harris, David (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Campus History (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - History-campus (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - History-fires and disasters (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - History-sports (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Housing (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Tower-building (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hoover Institution-Glenn Campbell (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hoover Institution-events (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hoover Institution-people, A-K (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hoover Institution-people, L-Z (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy, Donald (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Lake Lagunita (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Land (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Medical Center-Animal research (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center-Buildings and grounds (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Medical Center-Children's Hospital (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center-Children's Hospital (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Medical Center-facilities, staff, procedures, etc. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center-facilities, staff, procedures, etc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center-Life flight (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Medical Center-Palo Alto Hospital (Hoover Pavilion) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Medical Center-patients (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Memorial Church (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Murder and crime (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Overseas campuses (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Police and Fire (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Politicians on campus (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Primate farm (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Reagan Library (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Research (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Research (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Shultz, George (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Solar observatory (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sports-football (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sports-other (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sports-stadium (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center-site, exterior (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Stanford shopping center-shops and grounds (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Stanford shopping center-shops and grounds (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University Band (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stegner, Wallace (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sterling, J.E. Wallace (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Students campus activities (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Students campus activities (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Student demonstrations, 1959-1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Student demonstrations, 1980-85 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Student demonstrations, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Students-individuals (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Students-special achievements (Box 8, Folder 10)